

# BRANDON MCCRAY

**Software Engineer** 

### DETAILS

bradmccray89@gmail.com (757) 995-3444

#### PROFILE

Talented software engineer with 2 years of experience in working remotely, and 4 years of experience in building, maintaining, testing, and integrating software and web applications. Well-versed in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Angular, C#, NodeJs, Java, AWS, EC2, Firebase, Heroku, SQL, Linux, and Windows. As a veteran I also have 3+ years of leadership experience.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Software Engineer, Fairview, Raleigh, NC

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Overhauling outdated code base and implementing Angular across applications resulting in increased usability, portability, and reduced load time.
- Increasing application usability and consistency helping to increase revenue and client base.
- Implemented updated procedures to increase productivity and workflow

#### Software Engineer, Sharptop Co., Lynchburg, VA

AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2021

- Maintain and testing web applications through AWS.
- Coordinating with other software and business developers to evaluate and improve software.
- Developing code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.

#### Electronics Technician, U.S. Navy

MAY 2011 — JANUARY 2015

- Duties included running a work-center of 5 people.
- Scheduling and performing maintenance tasks and training in a timely manner.
- Performing acceptance testing and measurements on electronic components and assemblies to verify system compliance.

#### **EDUCATION**

Computer Science, Liberty University, Lynchburg, VA

AUGUST 2015 - JULY 2019

LINKS

Linkedin

## SKILLS

Angular HTML & CSS

Node.js Git

SQL Critical thinking and problem solving

## REFERENCES

References available upon request

## HOBBIES

video games, music, working on my discord bot, hiking